myflare.com 2015-03-15

# myflare Makes Cloud Storage Simple and Easy

We want you to know how we treat personal information we may obtain from you through our application and the use of our website. You should also see our [Terms of Use](https://www.myflare.com/terms.html) for other information concerning use of our application. By using our application, you accept both this Policy and our Agreement. 

####  Information We Collect 

Application Users – When you use our application, we (including our application service partners) collect access log and ecommerce transaction information as well information related to the number, size and type of files stored using the application. If this application is used through a browser, we may also collect information such as the Internet Protocol (IP) addresses assigned (numbers assigned to your computer while online), bandwidth used, system and connection performance, browsers used, dates and times of access, and Internet resource requests, including requests to access web pages. 

Cookies – If accessed through a browser, we may use "cookies" to collect information about your visit to our website and to manage information concerning your preferences. A "cookie" is a small computer code added to a file on your computer as a record of its visit. It does not collect or provide your name or any other personal information about you. It can, however, be used to note information about your visit, such as your type of web browser, operating system and Internet Protocol ("IP") address, to better tailor the site for you. It can also be used to recognize you when you log in as a registered user or as a repeat visitor returning to our website. This allows us to tailor our site by remembering you and any options you select. We may share non-personal information obtained from the varying kinds of cookies with vendors, advertisers and others. You can control what cookies are accepted by your computer through the settings on your web browser or by deleting them from your files. Doing so, however, may limit the personalization available to you. 

Third-Party Cookies and Web Beacons – These forms of computer code are sometimes placed in connection to a webpage. They may use a form of code called a "web beacon" or "clear GIF." These are usually contained in a transparent image on a page or in an image on an email message and serve as a way to gather information about your visit, such as your Internet Protocol Address and information or statistics about your visit. As with cookies, you can use your browser or app settings to control web beacons. 

Behavioral or Interest Based Ad Options – We and other website owners or advertisers may use cookies or similar tools to provide customized ads based on visits to their websites. You can find more information about these tools, including benefits they can provide at http://www.networkadvertising.org. Many companies that collect information for behavioral advertising are members of the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI). NAI offers the ability for you to opt-out of the behavioral advertising programs of their members by going to http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices. Please note that if you use a different computer, change your web browser, or delete your cookies, you will need to renew all of your opt-out choices. 

Advertisers and Other Websites – We do not control the privacy policies of advertisers or of websites you may link to from our website. You should review their websites for questions about their Internet security and privacy. 

####  Use and Sharing 

Use Policy – We consider any personally identifiable information we receive about you to be confidential, and it is our policy to use it only in providing our website and services - from sales to operations, administration, advertising, marketing, support, maintenance, billing, collection communications with you and similar ways. We may also use such information in dealing with fraud and unauthorized use of our application. We may associate personal account information with data from third parties about you or similar persons to better predict your product and service preferences, for use in advertising transactions and to market services to you. 

Aggregate Information – We use aggregate information about our customers and website visitors for a variety of purposes. Such aggregate information does not identify individual customers. We may share such aggregate and related demographic information with third parties. 

Retention Policy – We may retain personal customer information in our business records as long as someone is a customer or until no longer needed for business or legal purposes. 

Sharing Policy – It is our overall policy not to disclose to others outside of us and our affiliates, vendors and business partners any personally identifiable information or stored content without your prior consent. We do not sell or provide your personal information or stored content to parties unconnected with the services we provide without your permission. 

Special Exceptions – We reserve the right to disclose personally identifiable information or stored content in our possession if we have a good faith belief that it is necessary to: (1) comply with the law or legal process served on us; (2) protect and defend our rights or property or those of others; (3) respond to fraud, abuse or unauthorized use of our services; (4) enforce our [Terms of Use](https://www.myflare.com/terms.html) or related standards; or (5) act in an emergency to protect your safety or that of another. We may also share information if we sell or transfer all or a portion of our business operations, merge or combine with another organization. 

Third Parties – We use affiliates, vendors or third party partners in association with this application and may provide personally identifiable information about users for such purposes. In providing such information, we require that the third party maintain at least the same level of confidentiality that we maintain for such information. In addition, any use by the third party may not exceed that needed to provide its service. 

Internet Communications – We do not have access to any content stored by you as part of your use of this application. All content is encrypted in transit and in storage. Unless addressed to us, we do not read email messages or the content of other online communications. We may however, retain and provide such communications if we are legally required to do so. 

####  Law Enforcement 

Legal Requirements –We may receive legal requests for your information and content stored by you from government and law enforcement personnel. We may also receive discovery requests in civil litigation. In all such cases, our policy is to cooperate as required by law, but to provide only such information as the law requires. The law does permit us to disclose to law enforcement, voluntarily and without prior notice, customer information, including the contents of communications or content stored by you, if we reasonably believe that an emergency involving immediate danger of death or serious physical injury requires such disclosure without delay. 

####  Internet Security 

Taking Proper Precautions – Maintaining the security of your own personal computer is an important part of protecting your own privacy and of helping us protect our network and our customers’ service. You should use and update regularly your antivirus software, firewall and your operating system to prevent unauthorized access by others and harm from various forms of viruses. Persons with questionable intent may use the Internet or email to pose as someone you trust or do business with. You should always be sure who you are dealing with before responding with personal information. To avoid all these and other forms of attacks, we encourage you to visit the [Federal Trade Commission](http://www.ftc.gov/) for updates and tips on protecting yourself. 

Personal Information – We use "Secure Socket Layer" encryption technology when collecting certain personal information through our website and this application. We protect personally identifiable information using encrypted formats within controlled and secure environments with restricted access. While we attempt to ensure the integrity and security of our network and computer systems, we cannot guarantee that our security measures will prevent unauthorized access. 

####  Children's Privacy 

Our website and application are not directed at, or intended for use by, children under the age of 13. If you believe your child may have provided us with personal information, you can contact us and we will delete the information. You can find more information about protecting children’s privacy at the website of the FTC at http://www.ftc.gov. 

####  Changes in Policy 

Developments in the Internet, the law, our application and website may cause us to change this Privacy Policy from time to time. Changes are available through your application settings or on this webpage.
